<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<doc>
  <block header="What if google morphed into googleos?">
    <text> What if google expanded on its search-engine (and now e-mail) wares into a full-fledged operating system? [via microsoft watch from mary jo foley ] (and, by the way, is anybody else just a little nostalgic for the days when that was a good thing?) This buzzmachine post argues that google's rush toward ubiquity might backfire -- which we've all heard before, but it's particularly well-put in this post. Google is a nice search engine. Does anybody use it for anything else? They own blogger, of course. Is that a money maker? I'm staying away from the stock.</text>
    <text> I doubt the very few who actually read my blog have not come across this yet, but i figured i would put it out there anyways. John donovan from argghhh! Has put out a excellent slide show on what was actually found and fought for in fallujah. Click here to view it. He makes some good observations on a few of the pic's. One of the pictures shows a flag that was found in fallujah. On the next two pictures he took screenshots of two beheading video's. Compare the flags to the fallujah one. You have to see these slides....they are amazing. This fallujah operation my turn out to be the most important operation done by the us military since the end of the war.</text>
  </block>
  <block header=" IT’S GOOGLE">
    <text>Let me join the chorus of annoyance over google's new toolbar , which, as noted in the linked article, commits just about every sin an online marketer could commit, and makes up a few new ones besides. I'm not fond of the google-hates-privacy argument (you don't need to use their site, you can opt-out of sharing your information, you don't need to send stuff to anyone with a gmail account, and if -- wonder of wonders -- you're worried that you might send something to someone who would forward an excerpt to someone who would then store it on a gmail account... You have far, far too much time on your hands). However, this toolbar is really bad news. On the other hand, it looks pretty cool.</text>
    <text> Iran says it is creating nuclear energy without wanting nuclear weapons. The united states doesn't believe the iranian government. One can suspect the iranian government. But there is no proof . I read an article in time magazine accusing the iranian government of being willing to start a nuclear war and i sympathise with the article. They are certainly being nasty to the united nations security council in connection with the anti-proliferation treaty. </text>
  </block>
</doc>
